Guide to the Kenneth J. Arrow Papers, 1939-2011
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Correspondence and Personal Files Series, 1980s-1990s.
  - Lewis, Alain, 6 folders (Box 23)
  - Lewis, Alain, 1986-89, 4 folders (Box 23)
  - Lewis, Alain, 5 folders (Box 49)
  - Light, Daniel (Box 23)
  - Li Calzi, Marco (Box 23)
  - Limes, Jack L. (Box 23)
  - Lin, Kuan-Pin (Box 23)
  - Lin, Kuan-Pin (Box 49)
  - Lines, Jack (Box 23)
  - Lumsden, Keith G. (Box 23)
  - Lumsden, Keith G., The Esmee Fairbairn Research Center- Hariot Watt University (Box 23)
  - Luo, Yuanzheng (Box 23)
  - M, misc. (Box 23)
  - M, misc., (2 folders) (Box 49)
  - Machina, Mark (Box 23)
  - Maier Inflation Project (Box 23)
  - McAllister, P. (Box 23)
  - McCloskey, Donald (Box 24)
  - McKenzie, Lionel (Box 24)
  - Mckay, Chris (Box 24)
  - McLean, Dr. Iain (Box 24)
  - McNeil, Barbara, 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Malcomson, James (Box 24)
  - Mandel, Michael (Box 24)
  - Mankin, Wyatt B. (Box 24)
  - Manne, Alan (Box 24)
  - Marchi, E., 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Margolis, Julius, 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Marks, David (Box 24)
  - Marks, Robert E. (Box 24)
  - Marshak, Jacob and Robert (Box 24)
  - Marschak memoirs (Box 24)
  - Marshall, John (Box 24)
  - Mas- Colell, Andreu (Box 24)
  - Mash, Vladimir (Box 24)
  - Maskin, Eric, 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Masse, Pierre (Box 24)
  - Menell, Peter (Box 24)
  - Mermerci, Mehmet A. (Box 24)
  - Mesthene, Emmanuel G. (Box 24)
  - Mezhlumian, A. (Box 49)
  - Milgrom, Paul Robert (Box 24)
  - Miller, Margaret (Box 24)
  - Miller, Ross (Box 24)
  - Mo, Jie-Ping (Box 24)
  - Montgomery, David (Box 24)
  - Morgan, Christol (Box 24)
  - Moss, Jonathan (Box 24)
  - Moss, Scott (Box 24)
  - Moulin, Herve (Box 24)
  - Moynihan, Daniel Patrick (Box 24)
  - Minhas, Bagicha (Box 24)
  - Miyao, Takahiro (Box 24)
  - Myerson, Roger, 2 folders (Box 24)
  - N, misc. (Box 24)
  - Nakatani, Iwao, 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Namias, Jerome (Box 24)
  - Nishino, Hisakazu (Box 24)
  - Neff, Thomas L. (Box 24)
  - Nerlove, Marc, 3 folders (Box 24)
  - Neuberg, Leland (Box 24)
  - Nevo (Box 24)
  - Neyman, Abraham (Box 24)
  - Noll, Roger (Box 24)
  - Novshek (Box 24)
  - O, misc. (Box 24)
  - O, misc (Box 49)
  - O'Hara, Ryan (Box 24)
  - O'Reilly, Terrance, 2 folders (Box 24)
  - O'Reilly, Terrance (Box 25)
  - Osana, Hiroaki (Box 25)
  - Ostroy, Joseph (Box 25)
  - P, misc. (Box 25)
  - P, misc (Box 49)
  - Panthaki, Farrakh (Box 25)
  - Papadopoulos, Nicholas, 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Papadopoulos, Nicholas (Box 49)
  - Parrillo, Richard Case (Box 25)
  - Pattanaik, Prasanta K. (Box 25)
  - Prazner, Elisha and David Schmeidler (Box 25)
  - Polemarchakis, Heraklis (Box 25)
  - Parikh, Prashant, 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Peleg, Bezalel (Box 25)
  - Pesochinsky, Leon (Box 25)
  - Peterson, Louis D. (Box 25)
  - Phelps, Edward S. (Box 25)
  - Phelps, G.S. (Box 49)
  - Phillips, Tony, 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Pitbladdo Jr., Richard (Box 25)
  - Pliska, Stanley (Box 25)
  - P'ng, Ivan (Box 25)
  - Pope, Robin (Box 25)
  - Postlewaite, Andrew (Box 25)
  - Poterba, James (Box 25)
  - Prescott, Ed (Box 25)
  - Psomas, Andreas (Box 25)
  - Quint, Tom, 1993 (Box 25)
  - R, misc. (Box 25)
  - R, misc. (Box 49)
  - Radner, Roy (Box 25)
  - Radner, Roy (Box 49)
  - Raduchel, William J. (Box 25)
  - Raduchel Dissertation (Box 25)
  - Ramey, Garey (Box 25)
  - Rao, N. Koteswara (Box 25)
  - Rapping, Leonard A. (Box 25)
  - Rassias, Themistocles M. (Box 25)
  - Ratner, Sidney (Box 25)
  - Raven, Peter H. (Box 25)
  - Ray, Debraj (Box 25)
  - Reich, Michael, 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Restrepo, Prof R.A. (Box 25)
  - Richardson (Box 25)
  - Rieder, Alyssa (Box 25)
  - Riis, Christian (Box 25)
  - Riley, John (Box 25)
  - Riveria (Box 25)
  - Robbertson III, James F. (Box 25)
  - Robinson Lectures (Box 25)
  - Rogerson, Bill (Box 25)
  - Roemer, John E. (Box 25)
  - Rosen, Sherwin (Box 25)
  - Rosenschein, Jeffrey S. (Box 25)
  - Rossol, Joshua (Box 25)
  - Roth, Alvin (Box 25)
  - Roughgarden, Jeffrey (Box 25)
  - Rowley, Jennifer L. (Box 25)
  - Rubinstein, Ariel (Box 25)
  - S, misc. (Box 25)
  - S, misc., 3 folders (Box 49)
  - Schaefer, Mark E. (Box 25)
  - Sheshinksi, Eytan (Box 25)
  - Sheshinksi, Eytan (Box 49)
  - Skaf, Mazen (Box 49)
  - Spence, A.M. (Box 25)
  - Spence, Mike (Box 25)
  - Stan, Peter (Box 25)
  - Stan, Peter (Box 49)
  - Starr, Ross (Box 26)
  - Starrett, David A. (Box 26)
  - Starrett, David A. (Box 49)
  - Sterling Resolution, 1985 (Box 26)
  - Stoetzel, Jean (Box 26)
  - Stoleru, L. (Box 26)
  - Strasnick, Steve (Box 26)
  - Sutch, Richard (Box 26)
  - Swinton, David (Box 26)
  - Stokey, Nancy (Box 26)
  - Szenberg, Michael (Box 49)
  - T, misc. (Box 26)
  - Takatoshi, Ito (Box 26)
  - Tandon, Pankaj (Box 26)
  - Thain, Eric (Box 26)
  - Trosper, Ron, 2 folders (Box 26)
  - U, misc. (Box 26)
  - V, misc. (Box 26)
  - Virmandi, Arvind (Box 26)
  - Viscusi, W. Kip (Box 26)
  - W, misc. (Box 26)
  - Werbos, Paul (Box 26)
  - Wesson Latin America (Box 26)
  - White, Lawrence H. (Box 26)
  - Yanofsky, Neal (Box 26)
  - X, misc. (Box 26)
  - Y,Z misc. (Box 26)
  - Harvard University, Project on Efficiency in Decision Making in Economic Systems, KJA References Correspondence, 4 folders (Box 26)
  - Harvard University, Project on Efficiency in Decision Making in Economic Systems, KJA References Correspondence, 18 folders (Box 27)
- Notes, Papers, and Research Series, 1939-1994 (bulk 1972-1994).
  This series will likely be of most interest to scholars of Professor Arrow's contributions to economic theory. While, like the other series, the bulk of this series dates after 1970, it does include files from earlier periods. The Class Notes and Theses Subseries contains notes from his undergraduate courses at City College of New York and graduate courses at Columbia University, including notes from Professor H. Hotelling's course in Mathematical Economics and a penultimate draft of his Masters Thesis. It also includes notes on meteorology in preparation for his work in the Army Air Corps. A subseries on Notes and Papers by Arrow also contains earlier work. The most extensive files in this subseries include notes on optimization and decentralization, a National Science Foundation project on production functions, stability, and uncertainty.
  The rest of the series contains work dating after 1970. The Notes for papers by Arrow Subseries contains drafts and notes for specific papers. The Ongoing Grants Subseries contains several projects funded by the National Science Foundation and the Office of Naval Research. The Notes Subseries contains files of notes relating to various topics, but seemingly unconnected to any specific paper. The last subseries, Festschrift and papers in the history of economic thought, contains files on those activities.
  - Class Notes and Theses (City College of NY and Columbia) Subseries, 1939-1943 (Box 28)
    - 1939 (?) Philosophy Classes (Nature of Mathematics, Philosophy of Mathematics, Consistency of a Mathematical System) (Box 28)
    - 1939-40 Honors Essays (Quaternions and Mathematical Statistics) (Box 28)
    - 1940 (?) Educational Psychology (Mexican Civilization) (Box 28)
    - 1940 Masters Thesis (Stochastic Processes, under Harold Hotelling), drafts (Box 28)
    - 1940 (?) Economics of Social Insurance (Actuarial Basis of Unemployment Insurance) and Mathematical Economics (with Harold Hotelling) (Box 28)
    - 1940-41 Theory of Functions (Jordan Separation Theorem and Prime Number Theorem) (Box 28)
    - 1941-42 Current Types of Economic Theory (Box 28)
    - 1943 Meteorology (Box 28)
  - Notes, Papers by Arrow, and Papers by Others Subseries, 1950-1978
    - Allocation of Risk Bearing by Arrow (Box 28)
    - Arrow reprints ( Alternative Approaches to the Theory of Choice in Risk-Taking Situations, 1952, Uncertainty and the Welfare Economics of Medical Care, 1963, Comments on Dusenberry's The Portfolio Approach to the Demand for Money and Other Assets, 1963, Control in Large Organizations, 1964 ) (Box 28)
    - Equilibrium optimality, 1960 and 1968 (Box 28)
    - Equilibrium and uniqueness (includes correspondence with Frank Hahn) (Box 28)
    - The Firm in General Equilibrium Theory by Arrow, 1969 (Box 28)
    - Granger, C.W.J.-reprints (Box 28)
    - Optimal growth in linear models, 1965 (Box 28)
    - Optimal growth, 1965-67, 1974, 1978 (Box 28)
    - Optimization and Decentralization, 1950-60 (Box 28)
      (notes, including “on marginal cost pricing,” and “convergence of the limiting form of the gradient method;” correspondence with William Gorman and Leonid Hurwicz; paper by Morton Slater; paper by Arrow and Hurwicz, Decentralization and Computation and Resource Allocation; paper by Arrow Optimization, Decentralization, and Internal Pricing in Business Firms)
    - Production functions
      - NSF proposal, 1960-64 (Box 28)
      - Chenery- Solow proposal (project on production functions), 1964-70 (Box 28)
      - Bibliography, 1969 (Box 28)
      - CES fits (Box 28)
      - Elasticities (Box 28)
      - Embodiment, 1962-66 (Box 28)
      - Learning-by-doing (includes correspondence with Joan Robinson), 1962-68 (Box 28)
      - Murata, 1966 (Box 28)
      - NSF reporting, 1964-65 (Box 28)
      - Non-neutral progress, 1968 (Box 28)
      - Relations to growth models, 1968 (Box 28)
      - Statistical methods, 1965 (Box 28)
    - Recognizing the Maximum of a Sequence, by John Gilber and Frederick Mosteller, 1966 (Box 28)
    - Stability I, 1950s and 1960s (Box 29)
      (includes notes; papers and drafts by R.W. Clower, David Gale, Takashi Negishi, Trout Rader, Stanley Reiter, and Robert Wilson; and paper by Arrow and Hurwicz, Some Remarks on the Equilibria of Economic Systems)
    - Stability II, 1950s and 1960s (Box 29)
      (includes notes; notes from Maurice Allais; correspondence with Hurwicz; papers by Herbert Scarf, Frank Hahn, Hahn and Negishi, Lionel McKenzie, Peter Newman; and paper Arrow and Hurwicz, Competitive Stability Under Weak Gross Substitutability)
    - Stability III, 1950s and 1960s (Box 29)
      (notes, including “unique stable equilibrium with one inferior good;”; lectures; correspondence with Hurwicz; papers by Clower, Hahn, Negishi)
    - Uncertainty I, 1960s (Box 29)
      (includes correspondence with G.O. Bierwag, William Brainard, Jacques Drèze, Lucien Foldes, Alvin Klevorick, and others; draft by Arrow Optimal Allocation of Risk Bearing)
    - Uncertainty II, 1960s (Box 29)
      (drafts; paper by Arrow, Aspects of Theory of Risk Bearing)
    - Uncertainty III, 1960s (Box 29)
      (notes, including “theory of flood control;” paper by Henry Allen Latané)
    - Uncertainty IV, 1960s (Box 29)
      (paper by Arrow and Robert Lind Uncertainty and the Valuation of Public Investment Decisions)
    - Uncertainty V, 1960s (Box 29)
      (notes, including “adverse selection”; notes from Gerard Debreu and Leo Tornquist; lectures; drafts; paper by Richard Nelson)
  - Notes for papers by Arrow Subseries, 1973-1994
    - Collected Papers of Arrow
      - correspondence (Box 29)
      - head notes (Box 29)
      - pictures (Box 29)
    - The Demand for Information and the Distribution of Income, 1985-86 (Box 29)
    - The Division of Labor in the Economy, The Polity, and Society (Box 29)
    - The Economics of 1984, 1984 (Box 29)
    - Economic Science in the Future, 1990 (Box 29)
    - Economic Theory of Organization (Box 29)
    - Energy (Box 29)
    - The Short View and the Long, 1985 (Box 29)
    - Equilibrium in Economics, 1987-90 (Box 29)
    - Excellence and Equity in Higher Education, 1990-93 (Box 29)
    - General Economic Equilibrium, 1973 (Box 29)
    - The Genesis of Dynamic Systems Governed by Metzler Matrices, 1976 (Box 29)
    - Income Testing and Social Welfare (Box 29)
    - Informational Equivalence of Signals (Box 29)
    - Information and Economic Behavior, 1973 (Box 29)
    - Innovation in Large and Small Firms (Box 29)
    - An Interview with Kenneth J. Arrow (by Jerry Kelly), 1986 (Box 29)
    - Is the World Going Socialist? (Box 29)
    - The Limits of the Market in Resource Allocation (with Steven Shavell and Janet Yellen), 1976 (Box 29)
    - Microeconomic Simulation Models (Box 29)
    - Comments (Box 29)
    - Neoclassical Theory and its Discontents, 1993-94 (Box 29)
    - Notes on Expectations Equilibria in Bayesian Settings (with Jerry Green), 1973 (Box 29)
    - On a Theorem of Arrow (Box 29)
    - Comment, 1974 (Box 29)
    - Origins of the Impossibility Theorem, 1991 (Box 29)
    - Optimal Pricing, Use, and Exploration of Uncertain Natural Resource Stocks (with Sheldon Chang), 1978 (Box 29)
    - Proposed Reforms of the Economic System of Information and Decision in the USSR (with Edmund Phelps), 1990 (Box 29)
    - A Production Function for the Repairman Problem (with David Levhari and Eytan Sheshinski), 1970 (Box 29)
    - Rationality of Self and Others in an Economic System, 1986-88 (Box 29)
    - Rate of Discount on Investments with Imperfect Capital Markets (notes from Martin Feldstein) (Box 29)
    - Search, Equilibrium, and Information (with Michael Rothschild), 1973 (Box 29)
    - Social Choice and Multicriterion Decision-Making (with Hervé Reynaud), 1987 (Box 30)
    - Spatial Allocation of Non-Educational Public Expenditure/Public Investment for Optimal Development (Box 30)
    - Technical Information, Returns to Scale, and the Existence of Competitive Equilibrium, 1985-86 (Box 30)
    - Uncertainty in Energy Planning, 1979 (Box 30)
    - Handbook of Mathematical Economics, 1976-79 (Box 30)
    - Handbook Series, 1979-93 (Box 31)
  - Ongoing Grants Subseries, 1973-1992
    - National Science Foundation (NSF)
      - Unification of Comparative Statics and Comparative Dynamics in General Equilibrium Models (with Peter Kalman), 1974-77 (Box 31)
      - Social Associations Under Varying Market Structures (with Mordecai Kurz), 1980 (Box 31)
      - Economic Interaction under Bounded Rationality and Limited Memory, 1986-92 (Box 31)
      - Intrafirm and Interfirm Information Flows, 1982-84 (Box 31)
      - Technology Assessment and Risk Analysis (TARA), 1982-87 (Box 31)
      - Imperfect Competition and Price Stability in Competitive Equilibrium (with Frank Hahn), 1987 (Box 31)
      - Informational and Organizational Impacts on Productivity (with Paul David, et al.), 1987-91 (Box 31)
      - Information as an Economic Commodity (with Kurz and Robert Aumann), 1990-91 (Box 31)
      - Dynamic Pricing Policies: Dupoly Equilibrium and Information (with Eytan Sheshinski), 1989-93 (Box 31)
    - ONR (Box 32)
      - Annual Proposals, 1974-88 (Box 50)
      - Budget, 1981-82 (Box 50)
      - Budget, 1984-85 (Box 50)
      - Center, (3 folders) (Box 50)
      - Correspondence, 1969-79, (2 folders) (Box 50)
      - ONR General, 1979-91 (Box 31)
      - Mark Machina Article, 1983 (Box 32)
      - Official Contracts Data, 1973-74 (Box 50)
      - Renewal Project, 1977-78 (Box 50)
      - Renewal Project, 1981-82 (Box 50)
      - Report Production, 1968-78 (Box 50)
      - Urban Institute, 1973-76 (Box 32)
  - Notes Subseries, 1972-1985, undated
    - Arrow/Hahn-Sienna Book Negotiations, 1977 (Box 50)
    - Arrow/Hahn, Plans for revision, 1977 (Box 50)
    - Articles- Kevin McCabe et al., Vernon Smith, Daniel Kahneman, Elliot Montroll, Marcello de Cecco, Partha Dasgupta and Joseph Stiglitz, Seppo Honkopohja, Michael Lovell (Box 32)
    - Classical Famine, 1983 (Box 32)
    - Cournot Oligopoly, 1979 (Box 32)
    - Decentralization (Box 32)
    - Decentralization II (Box 32)
    - Demand for Supplementary Health Insurance, 1974 (Box 50)
    - Duopoly (Box 32)
    - Dynamic Monopoly Pricing (Box 32)
    - Dynamic Systems (Box 32)
    - The Economy of Israel, 1984 (Box 32)
    - Energy, 1972-79, 1985 (Box 32)
    - EPA Discount Rate, 1982 (Box 50)
    - Excerpt from The Collected Mathematical Papers of Arthur Cayley (Box 32)
    - Inflation-Remarks by William Fellner and Alan Greenspan, 1974 (Box 32)
    - Miscellaneous Notes (Box 32)
    - Nonlinear Metzler System (Box 32)
    - OPEC Pricing (Box 32)
    - Demand Reduction (Box 32)
    - Optimal Pricing and Natural Resources, 1980 (Box 50)
    - Organization Theory Group (Box 32)
    - Permanent Income as Welfare (Box 32)
    - Racial Discrimination (Box 32)
    - Social Choice-Correspondence and Notes (Box 32)
    - Tax Reform (Box 32)
    - Technology Assessment (Box 32)
    - Value of Life (Box 32)
  - Notes Subseries, 1986-2010 (Box 50)
    - Antibiotic Study, 2005-07 (Box 50)
    - Arrow/Hahn-Sienna, 1998, (2 folders) (Box 50)
    - Debreu-Kirman, 1997 (Box 50)
    - Education Department, 1995-96 (Box 50)
    - Employment Security, ND (Box 50)
    - Increasing Returns, 2000 (Box 50)
    - JEP Discrimination, 1998 (Box 50)
    - Levin Paper, 2007 (Box 50)
    - Nikkei Op-Ed, 1997 (Box 50)
    - Rational Choice and Humanities, 2006 (Box 50)
    - Sethi Paper, 2009 (Box 50)
    - Smith-Richardson Proposal, 2003-04 (Box 50)
    - Socialist Reform, 1990 (Box 50)
    - Socialist Reform, 1991 (Box 50)
    - Times Literary Supplement on Higher Education, 1999 (Box 50)
    - World Sustainability, 2006 (Box 50)
    - World Sustainability, 2007 (Box 51)
    - Handbooks Series, 1988-98 (Box 51)
    - Handbook of Social Choice and Welfare, 1997-98 (Box 51)
    - Handbook of Social Choice and Welfare, 2000 (Box 51)
    - Handbooks-Sheshinksi, 1989-90 (Box 51)
  - Festschrift and Papers on the History of Economics Subseries, 1970s to 1990s (Box 32)
    - Arrow, Kenneth-Festschrift (Box 32)
    - Beckman, Martin-Festschrift (Box 32)
    - Bergson, Abram-Festschrift (Box 32)
    - Black, Duncan-Festschrift (Box 32)
    - Borch, Karl-Festschrift (Box 32)
    - Ehrlich, Alexander-Festschrift (Box 32)
    - Fitoussi, Jean-Paul-Festschrift, 2002 (Box 51)
    - Galbraith, John Kenneth-Festschrift (Box 32)
    - Hahn, Frank-Festschrift (Box 32)
    - Harsanyi, John-Festschrift (Box 32)
    - Hotelling, Harold-Festschrift (Box 32)
    - Houthakker, Henk-Festschrift (Box 32)
    - Hurwicz, Leonid-Festschrift (Box 32)
    - Kantorovich, L.V.-Festschrift (Box 32)
    - Karlin, Sam-Festschrift (Box 32)
    - Krutilla, John-Festschrift (Box 32)
    - Lerner, Abba-Festschrift (Box 32)
    - Labini, Sylos-Festschrift (Box 32)
    - Lieberman, Gerald-Festschrift (Box 51)
    - Lipinski, Edward-Festschrift (Box 32)
    - Reder, Mel-Festschrift (Box 32)
    - Robinson, Joan-Festschrift (Box 32)
    - Sen, Amartya-Festschrift (Box 51)
    - Shubik, Martin-Festschrift (Box 32)
    - Stiglitz, Joseph-Festschrift (Box 51)
    - Suppes, Patrick-Festschrift (Box 32)
    - Vickrey, William-Volume of Collected Papers (Box 32)
    - Von Neumann, John-Festschrift (Box 32)
    - Keynes's Treatise on Probability (Box 32)
    - Klassiker der Nationalokonomie (Edgeworth's Ethics and Ricardo's Work as Viewed by Later Economists) (Box 32)
    - Marshak, Jacob-Portrait (Box 33)
    - Marshak Recollections (Box 33)
    - Thorstein Veblen as an Economic Theorist (Box 33)
- Stanford and Harvard Series, 1948-1994 (bulk 1970-1994).
  Includes committee, consulting, volunteer, and other work for his universities and their economics departments. It also includes lectures notes and reading materials for courses that Arrow has taught at Stanford and Harvard. It is comprised of the Stanford University Subseries, the Stanford Economics Department Subseries, the Stanford Course Material Subseries, the Harvard University and Economics Department Subseries, and the Harvard Course Material Subseries.
  - Stanford University Subseries (Box 33)
    - Alumni
      - 1985-87 (Box 33)
      - Bakersfield, 1987 (Box 33)
      - New York, 1983 (Box 33)
    - Centennial Campaign, 1986-89 (Box 33)
    - COGEE, 1996 (Box 51)
    - Entering Student Talk, 1983 (Box 33)
    - Ethics and Society Postdoctoral Fellowship, 1986-92 (Box 33)
    - Extradepartmental Education, 1984-85 (Box 33)
    - Engineering Research Center Proposal, 1985 (Box 33)
    - Faculty Report, 1983-84 (Box 33)
    - Football Recruiting, 1990 (Box 33)
    - Fundamental Standard (Stanford Speech Code), 1989 (Box 33)
    - Gardner Fellowship, 1985-89 (Box 33)
    - Ground Rent Task Force, 1985-89 (Box 33)
    - Health and Safety Review, 1988-90 (Box 34)
    - Homeowners Governance, 1989 (Box 34)
    - Hoover Institution, 1981-94, (2 folders) (Box 34)
    - Housing, 1981-83 (Box 34)
    - Humanities Center, 1983-91 (Box 34)
    - Humanities and Sciences Council, 1986 (Box 34)
    - Mathematical Sciences Education, 1984-85 (Box 34)
    - Medical Non-Tenure, 1986-87 (Box 34)
    - Public Service Requirement, 1990 (Box 34)
    - Reagan Library, 1986 (Box 34)
    - Research Committee, 1992 (Box 34)
    - Seltzer Endowed Book Fund, 1988 (Box 34)
    - South Africa, 1986 (Box 34)
    - Stanford Appointment, 1978-79 (Box 51)
    - Stanford Negotiations and Correspondence, 1974-79 (Box 34)
    - Stanford Pioneers, 2009 (Box 51)
    - Stanford Retreat, 1990 (Box 34)
    - Stanford Senate, 1987-89 (Box 34)
    - Stanford Senate, Western Culture Debate, 1985-88 (Box 34)
    - Stanford Summer, 1979 (Box 34)
    - Stanford University Project for Environmental Research (SUPER), 1990 (Box 34)
    - TSEMI, 1991 (Box 34)
  - Stanford, Department of Economics Subseries
    - Alternative Approaches Field, 1986-88 (Box 34)
    - Building, 1991 (Box 34)
    - Department Computer, 1988 (Box 34)
    - Economics Department (Memos and Meetings), 1983-94 (Box 34)
    - Economics Department (Memos and Meetings), 2003-04 (Box 51)
    - Environmental Economics Appointment, 1990-92 (Box 34)
    - Japan Trade Studies, 1985 (Box 34)
    - Job Market, 1979 (Box 35)
    - Operations Research, 1990-91 (Box 35)
    - Political Economics, 1985-86 (Box 35)
    - Population Studies (Box 35)
    - Visiting Scholars, 1986 (Box 35)
  - Stanford Course Material Subseries
    - Economics 185/285: The Distribution of Income and Wealth, 1985-95 (Box 51)
    - Economics 186/Philosophy 077: The Ethics of Social Decisions, 1992-93 (Box 35)
    - Economics 280/Operations Research 367: Welfare Economics, 1982-83 (Box 51)
    - Economics 282/Operations Research 363: Theory of Information and Organization, 1984-91 (Box 35)
    - Economics 386/Operations Research 366: Interdisciplinary Seminar on Conflict Resolution, 1981-93 (Box 35)
    - Economics 388/Operations Research 369: Interdisciplinary Seminar on Risk Management, 1981-91 (Box 35)
    - Micro Econ XX (Box 51)
    - Optimal Economics Growth, 1967 (Box 35)
    - Statistics Examinations, 1948-66 (Box 35)
  - Harvard University and Department of Economics Subseries
    - Audit, 1981 (Box 35)
    - Board of Syndics (Box 35)
    - Department of Economics, 1974-77 (Box 35)
    - Department of Economics, Macroeconomics Search, 1971 (Box 35)
    - Department of Economics, Faculty Appointments, 1989-93 (Box 35)
    - Faculty Council Elections, 1976 (Box 35)
    - Harvard Faculty Council, ND (Box 51)
    - Harvard Overseers, 1994 (Box 51)
    - Harvard Move (negotiations and correspondence), 1966-67 (Box 35)
    - Houses, 1970-74 (Box 35)
    - International Studies Committee, 1976-77 (Box 35)
    - Kirkland House, 1974-79 (Box 35)
    - Miscellaneous, 1974-79 (Box 35)
    - South Africa, 1979 (Box 35)
    - Wells Prize, 1978 (Box 35)
    - Women Hiring Practices, 1975 (Box 35)
    - Harvard Overseers, 1986-91 (Box 35)
  - Harvard Course Material Subseries
    - Economics 205 (Box 35)
    - Price and Allocation Theory (Box 35)
    - Economics 215: The Theory of Competitive Equilibrium, 1967 (Box 36)
    - Economics 225: The Theory and Estimation of Production Functions, 1969 (Box 36)
    - Economics 2010a, 1973 (Box 36)
    - Liquidity Preference (Box 36)
- Miscellaneous Series, 1950-1993 (bulk 1970s-1993).